Glucksman Ireland House Records AIA.038
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Glucksman Ireland House Activities and Administrative Files, 1907-2002 (inclusive); 1991-2002 (bulk); 3.77 Linear Feet in 5 legal sized manuscript boxes, 1 letter sized manuscript box, 1 half letter sized manuscript box, 1 shared media box, 1 shared CD box, and 1 shared flat box; 1.70 G
  - Hartford Conference, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Heaney, undated (Box 15, Betacam sp 038.023)
  - Hector McDonnell Art Exhibit Postcards, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - IAS Scans 1, AOH Bannon Shot, C 2000 AIA iMovie, undated (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_AIA_038_ER_052)
  - IAS Scans 2, undated (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_AIA_038_ER_050)
  - IH 008, undated (Box 16, Minidv 038.048)
  - IH/AIA C.A.T. Transcripts of Video Interviews, 2000 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_AIA_038_ER_053)
  - IH Program, Spring 1994 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - IH Staff Meetings, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Installation of Officers of the County Longford Men's S & B Association and Ladies Auxiliary, 1942 (Box Shared Tamiment 080, Folder 9)
  - International Programs Dublin, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Ireland House, undated (Box 14, Vhs 038.013)
  - Ireland House: Archives of Irish America Tapes Information & Transcripts, 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Ireland House at NYU Membership Application, undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Ireland House Press, 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Ireland House Roll #8, 2002 (Box 15, Vhs 038.015)
  - Ireland House Roll #9, 2002 (Box 15, Vhs 038.016)
  - Ireland House - Seq. 5/Seq 6, 2000 (Box 16, Minidv 038.047)
  - Irish Advisory Committee, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Irish Film Festival - Filmmaker Bios & Contact Sheet, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Irish Football Team Photos, 1932-1935 (Box Shared Tamiment 080, Folder 8)
  - Irish Hunger Commem. AOH Coalition, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Irish Institute, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Irish Language, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Irish Migration, undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Irish Studies Program, 1994-1997 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Irish Studies Program Fall Schedule, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - "Jameson Global Bloomsday" Program, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Joe Lee (cont'd) NYU Ireland House CR #4, 2000 (Box 16, Minidv 038.041)
  - John Feighery, 1943-1962 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - John W. Draper Interdisciplinary Master's Program in Humanities and Social Thought, undated (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - "The Kindgdom of Kerry" - Michael Flaherty Exhibition, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - L.B.G. Board, undated (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - List of Irish Writers and Books for Bobst, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Loretta, undated (Box 15, Betacam sp 038.022)
  - Loretta Brennan Glucksman, Cormac O'Malley 2, Bob Scally NYU Ireland House CR #2, 2000 (Box 16, Minidv 038.039)
  - Marion Scans Irish AM, 2000 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_AIA_038_ER_058)
  - Medieval Search, 1992-1994 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Memorandum, 1995-1997 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - NEH, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - New Asst. Prof. AD, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - "New York Stories" - The Archives of Irish America, 2000 (Box 16, Minidv 038.042)
  - New York Times, 1991, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - New York University Glucksman Ireland House Promo Video - Seq 5 (Work in Progress), 2000 (Box 15, Vhs 038.018)
  - New York University Irish Studies, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Next Door Neighbors: The Irish & others in New York City, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - NYCH - Bruce Arnold, 1994-1997 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - NYU in Dublin, undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - NYU Graduate School of Arts & Sciences Fall Course List, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - NYU Ireland House Tape #5 Pete Hamill Interview, 2000 (Box 14, Vhs 038.007, Box 16, Dvcam 038.024, Minidv 038.044)
  - NYU Ireland House Tape #6 Pete Hamill Interview Pt. 2, 2000 (Box 14, Vhs 038.008, Box 16, Dvcam 038.025, Minidv 038.045)
  - NYU Ireland House Tape #7 (IH/Bobst Ext.), 2000 (Box 14, Vhs 038.009, Box 16, Dvcam 038.026, Minidv 038.046)
  - NYU Ireland House Tape #8, 2000 (Box 16, Dvcam 038.027)
  - NYU Ireland House Tape #9, 2000 (Box 16, Dvcam 038.028)
  - Oliva, Neeson, Richardson, Donaghue, undated (Box 15, Betacam sp 038.021)
  - "On Being a Living Fossil: Writing in Irish", undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Padraig O'Cearuill, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Peter Quinn, Joe Lee NYU Ireland House CR #3, 2000 (Box 16, Minidv 038.040)
  - Post Colonial Conditions Ireland in a Comparative Context - Opening Lectures, undated (Box 14, Vhs 038.010)
  - Post-Colonial Conditions: Ireland in a Comparative Context Symposium Programs, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - RADHARC: Chronicles of Glucksman Ireland House, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Robert (Roy) Fitzroy CV, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - RW D'Arcy, 1947 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - "Scannan '96", 1996 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Seamus Deane Notre Dame, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Seamus Heaney Dinner, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Topics in Early Modern Europe: Ireland and Scotland in Europe in the 16th and 17th Centuries, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Visions and Revisions: Recent Trends in Irish History and Literature, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - "When Time Began to Rant and Rage" Exhibit, undated (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Wild Geese, 1992-1995 (Box 12, Folder 22)